healthformula.com 2014-05-24

# Health Formula

### At HealthFormula.com, we take your privacy very seriously. Here's our policy in brief:

**We hate spam** , junk email, junk mail and unwanted phone calls. Therefore, **we won't email you or call you** unless we have a specific question about your order. **We don't collect your information** for any reason beyond your purchase -- and we won't release your information to other companies. **Period**.

Now - here's the official version:

### Full text of our privacy policy

We will never release any personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number or credit card information without your consent. During the checkout process, we collect personal information that we use only to process your order.

We will only share or disclose such information in order to conform to the edicts of the law; protect and defend the right or property of Health Formula, Inc.; or act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of its members or the public.

Secure ordering online   
This website uses technology called Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt any personal information you transmit to us online. We use 128-bit encryption, currently the strongest commercially available, to encrypt your order information. Your order is encrypted on your computer and decoded after it reaches our secure server. This information cannot be decrypted during transit.

You may also fax your order from the Order page.

**What information we collect and why**   
We collect personal information primarily so that we may process your order, but also so that we may enhance our services to you and make your shopping experience as easy and pleasant as possible. Our goal is to provide the best value on the products we sell, as well as the highest possible level of service.

In addition to personal information collected for purposes of processing your order, we may ask for the following information:

**Billing and Shipping Information**   
During the checkout process, we ask for your name, address, e-mail, telephone number and credit card information. This information is necessary for us to process your order and ship it to you. Basic personal information such as name, address and telephone number, but not credit card numbers, may be transmitted to contracted third parties solely for the purpose of shipping your order (for instance, UPS).

As described above, ordering on our website is safe and secure because we use Secure Socket Layer Technology, which encrypts the information you send to us. This information cannot be decrypted during transmission. The our secure ordering server is not accessible to 3rd parties.

**Retrieving Information**   
At any time, you may request from us the information we have collected from you. Simply contact us. To protect your privacy, we will only e-mail this information to the e-mail address associated with your order. No credit card information will be divulged. We are unable to give out personal information over the phone.

**"Cookies"**   
Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. Health Formula, Inc cookies do not contain any personal identification information, but they do enable us to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser's settings to prevent that. You can also delete all the cookies on your computer at any time.

Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on www.dermboutique.com - including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them online.

**Contact Us:**

You may write to us at:

Health Formula, Inc   
314 E. Dania Beach Blvd. #132   
Dania Beach, FL 33004-3028 - USA

Call us at 1-800-414-8009 or send us an email.
